Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XVI is arranged in 3 sub-series by Union file number.
Series XVII is arranged in 16 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XVI. NEGRO ORGANIZATIONS
  - Sub-Series 219-1. Negro Organizations
    - Sleeping Car Transportation. Pullman Company, Refund of one-half fare, 1920-1922 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 219-2. Negro Organizations
    - Sleeping Car Transportation. Pullman Company, Refund of one-half fare, 1947-1955 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Sleeping Car Transportation. Pullman Company, Refund of one-half fare, 1939-1941 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Sleeping Car Transportation. Pullman Company, Refund of one-half fare, 1929-1937 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Sleeping Car Transportation. Pullman Company, Refund of one-half fare, 1929 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 219-4. Negro Organizations
    - Sleeping Car Transportation. Pullman Company, Refund of one-half fare, 1927-1929 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Series XVII. LABOR NEWSPAPER
  - Sub-Series 220-0. Labor Newspaper
    - General, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      March 18, 1964-Dec. 31, 1964.
    - General, 1960-1964 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      Jan. 1, 1960-March 17, 1964.
    - General, 1955-1959 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      Aug. 1955-Dec. 31, 1959.
    - ("Labor") General, 1944-1955 (Box 66, Folder 10)
      1944-July 1955.
    - ("Labor") General, 1933-1943 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - General, 1930-1932 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Labor General, 1922-1929 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 220-1. Labor Newspaper
    - Financial Statements, 1963-1964 (Box 66, Folder 14)
      Jan. 1, 1963-Dec. 31, 1964.
    - Financial Statements, 1962 (Box 66, Folder 15)
      Jan. 1, 1962-Dec. 31, 1962.
    - Financial Statements, 1952-1961 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      1952-Dec. 31, 1961.
    - Labor Financial Statements, 1949-1951 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Labor Financial Statements, 1947-1948 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Labor Financial Statements, 1945-1946 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Labor Financial Statements, 1941-1944 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Labor Financial Statements, 1937-1940 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Labor Financial Statements, 1933-1936 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Labor Financial Statements, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Labor Financial Statements, 1931 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Labor Financial Statements, 1930 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Labor Financial Statements, 1926-1929 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 220-2. Labor Newspaper
    - Labor Finances and Meeting of Editors, 1920-1938 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 220-4. Labor Newspaper
    - Lodge Subscriptions-General, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      Aug. 1, 1965-Sept. 30, 1965.
    - Lodge Subscriptions-General, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      Jan. 1, 1965-July 31, 1965.
    - Lodge Subscriptions-General, 1933-1964 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      1933-Dec. 31, 1964.
    - Lodge Subscriptions-General, 1920-1929 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 220-5. Labor Newspaper
    - Labor Editorial Policy, 1921-1934 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 220-6. Labor Newspaper
    - Labor Executive Meetings and Subscription Drive, 1920 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 220-7. Labor Newspaper
    - Labor Articles For Publication, 1921-1932 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 220-8. Labor Newspaper
    - Labor Individual Subscriptions, 1932-1953 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Labor Individual Subscriptions, 1922-1930 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 220-9. Labor Newspaper
    - Labor Brotherhood Subscription, 1937-1949 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Labor Brotherhood Subscription, 1922 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Labor Brotherhood Subscription, 1922-1930 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 220-11. Labor Newspaper
    - Labor Cooperative Educational and Publishing Society, 1923-1930 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 220-12. Labor Newspaper
    - Labor Audit Report, 1933-1957 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 220-13. Labor Newspaper
    - Annual Meetings, Special Meetings, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 16)
      Jan. 1, 1965-Dec. 31, 1965.
    - Annual Meetings, Special Meetings, 1964 (Box 68, Folder 17)
      Jan. 1964-Dec. 31, 1964.
    - Annual Meetings, Special Meetings, 1963 (Box 68, Folder 18)
      Jan. 1, 1963-Dec. 31, 1963.
    - Annual Meetings, Special Meetings, 1960-1962 (Box 68, Folder 19)
      Jan. 1, 1960-Dec. 31, 1962.
    - Annual Meetings, Special Meetings, 1957-1959 (Box 68, Folder 20)
      Oct. 1957-Dec. 31, 1959.
    - Labor Annual and Special Meetings, Board of Directors, 1956-1957 (Box 68, Folder 21)
      Jan. 1956-Sept. 1957.
    - Labor Annual and Special Meetings, Board of Directors-Guy L. Brown, Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1955-1956 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Labor Annual and Special Meetings, Board of Directors, 1955 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      March 1955-Dec. 1955.
    - Labor Annual and Special Meetings, Board of Directors, 1947-1955 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      April 1947-Feb. 1955.
    - Labor Annual and Special Meetings, Board of Directors, 1941-1947 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      1941-March 1947.
    - Labor Annual and Special Meetings, Board of Directors, 1933-1940 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Labor Cooperative Educational and Publishing Society, 1924-1931 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 220-14. Labor Newspaper
    - Labor News Stand Subscriptions, 1924 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 220-15. Labor Newspaper
    - Labor Special Editions, 1924-1932 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 220-16. Labor Newspaper
    - Labor Proposed Increase In Managers Annual Salary -1924-25 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 220-18. Labor Newspaper
    - Labor Wages, 1933-1946 (Box 69, Folder 10)